hi everyone thank you for watching the
video today I'm going to show you how to
use YouTube and Artist summary powered
by hgbd extension and once you installed
it and you are ready to use the
summarization functions and if you go to
YouTube video you will see the small
widget and so if you click it and you
can see the transcript of the video like
this and if the video has other
languages you can choose a language you
want to view and then copy transcript or
you can jump to the current timestamp or
summarize the video like one click and
if we click it and it opens such EBD
then it automatically starts summarizing
then you can see the summary of the
video like this
and it actually works for like any web
pages too so this is a graph about page
and you see its content and you see this
small pop-up here yeah small icon here
if you click it and it's the same logic
you know as a YouTube summary but you
know you can summarize the content like
this so you can see what is grasp you
know how it works or you know some
information here
and let's say if you want to customize
you know your prompt and so on so
there's a user settings page so you can
choose you know dark mode light mode and
you know if you copy the transcript you
know you can choose markdown or plain
text and you can choose activity models
you know 3.5 for plugins routing if you
have access and and these models are
usually for you know the GPA plus users
as a paid users and if you're not you
know please select uh default but you
can choose other models but if you don't
access to it and it doesn't really work
and you can also choose languages like
you know English Chinese espanol you
know other languages like this and also
customize prompt and was key takeaways
from the following content or something
and and we are looking for better you
know prompt so if you found any if you
find any interest in prompts then please
let us know and you know and also we
have a strategy for longer videos or
contents and videos has a lot of
limitation and normally you can
summarize videos up to 30 minutes in
length you know in English and for
longer videos you know the the quality
of video you know it depends on you know
how you choose the videos let's say if
you watch 60 Minutes videos then but you
can only select you know just 20 minutes
so how do you choose any means and one
strategy is like a dividing 36 stimulus
content into equal resize chunks and
that's five minutes five minutes from
here from here something like that
that's all that you can grasp the big
pictures but it miss you know like some
some details right it's like a trailer
but another strategy is like at start to
the meaning type this up 0 to 20 minutes
so that it covers the details but you'll
miss the rest of 40 minutes
and the last one which is we don't
recommend using it but you know it's
like a just use entire content you know
whatever however long you know you use
entire content so usually you get the
error message from like touch video hey
the message too long and so on but
you know for some use cases maybe this
is useful so we keep it and yeah then
let's say you know you can choose this
somewhere like you know you see it's
more like here right sometimes it's
distracting so you can choose to make it
visible or hidden you know and and also
we have a keyboard shortcut like this so
if you hit Ctrl and X twice and you can
automatically summarize the content and
you can turn it off or on as you want so
and if you want to highlight the the web
page or trans you know YouTube videos
then we have another extension called
grasp so hope this helps you only it has
the same totally same functionality as
this you know YouTube and audio summary
powerwise hvd so yeah and this is how to
use you know this Chrome extension and
hope this helps your reading watching or
learning process and and also you know
in on grasp you know we have a you know
it's a community you know where people
sharing what they're reading watching
and learning so if you are interested in
you know please sign up and anyway
thanks for watching so hope you like it
and if you have any questions please let
us know you know our email address is
high at grass.co so yeah thanks so much
bye